<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learning Path - Trusted Committer on InnerSource Commons</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/</link><description>Recent content in Learning Path - Trusted Committer on InnerSource Commons</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing the Trusted Committer Role</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/01/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph pagenumrestart">
&lt;p>The Trusted Committer (TC) role is one of the key roles in an
InnerSource community. Think of Trusted Committers as the people in a community that
you trust with important technical decisions and with mentoring
contributors to ultimately get contributions over the finish line.
The Trusted Committer role is both demanding and rewarding. It is
more than just being an opinionated gatekeeper and is instrumental for
the success of any InnerSource community.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ensuring Product Quality</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/02/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>Let’s start with the responsibility most often associated with the Trusted Committer
role: ensuring product quality.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Keeping the Community Healthy</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/03/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>The introduction pointed out that Trusted Committers have both tech-oriented and
community-oriented responsibilities. It is not sufficient to focus on
code and code health only. To ensure success in the long run, Trusted Committers should
strive to keep the community building the software healthy
as well. Because of that, they must strike a good balance between ensuring product quality and growing a healthy community.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Upleveling Community Members</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/04/</guid><description>&lt;div id="upleveling" class="paragraph">
&lt;p>There is a continuum of participation in an InnerSource community.
There are people who are not aware of the community. &lt;em>Newcomers&lt;/em> might be interested in the community and its product, but have not yet used it. &lt;em>Consumers&lt;/em> use the software but may not have made a contribution. Then there are the &lt;a href="https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/contributor">&lt;em>Contributors&lt;/em>&lt;/a> who have made at least one contribution, and finally the &lt;em>Trusted Committers&lt;/em>, who are taking responsibility for both the software and the community.
As a Trusted Committer, you are responsible for moving individuals along this continuum
and upleveling their ability to make contributions. In this sense, Trusted Committers
act as force multipliers in their community.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lowering the Barriers to Entry</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/05/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>Soliciting contributions in an InnerSource community is more challenging than it is in an Open Source community for a number of reasons:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Advocating for the Community’s Needs</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/06/</guid><description>&lt;div id="advocating" class="paragraph">
&lt;p>InnerSource communities exist in a corporate context and are thus more constrained than Open Source communities. Sometimes the
business unit’s interests are at odds with those of the community.
Trusted Committers take a long term perspective on their project.
They understand that a healthy community is a precondition for healthy code.
This is why many InnerSource initiatives were modeled in the Apache Way with its &lt;a href="http://theapacheway.com/community-over-code/">"Community over Code"&lt;/a> motto.
Business units, on the other hand, are naturally more concerned with the products produced by an InnerSource community.
They prefer to see short to medium-term results that help the bottom line.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Becoming a Trusted Committer</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/07/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>The Trusted Committer role is a demanding but fulfilling role.
If this learning path interests you, you might be wondering how to actually become a Trusted Committer and if you are the right person for the job.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Conclusion</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/08/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>In the previous chapters we have learned about the responsibilities of Trusted Committers.
Some of these responsibilities include ensuring product quality, keeping their community healthy, reducing the barriers to making contributions, upleveling the community and advocating for its needs within the organization.
We also talked about how to become a Trusted Committer and what it takes to fulfill that role.
Working as a Trusted Committer is demanding but will ultimately amplify your value contribution in your company.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Workbook</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/workbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/workbook/</guid><description>&lt;div class="sect2">
&lt;h3 id="_video_the_trusted_committer_role_in_innersource">Video: The Trusted Committer Role in InnerSource&lt;/h3>
&lt;div class="sect3">
&lt;h4 id="_segment_introduction">SEGMENT: Introduction&lt;/h4>
&lt;div class="sect4">
&lt;h5 id="_question_1_what_sentence_best_describes_the_motivation_for_the_name_trusted_committer">Question 1. What sentence best describes the motivation for the name “Trusted Committer”?&lt;/h5>
&lt;div class="olist arabic">
&lt;ol class="arabic">
&lt;li>
&lt;p>They are the only ones that are trusted to make commits to the project.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>