<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sobre a InnerSource Commons on InnerSource Commons</title><link>/pt-br/about/</link><description>Recent content in Sobre a InnerSource Commons on InnerSource Commons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/pt-br/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fale Conosco</title><link>/pt-br/about/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pt-br/about/contact/</guid><description>A maneira mais rápida e melhor de nos contatar é entrar no Slack e fazer sua pergunta no canal #general.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Code of Conduct</title><link>/pt-br/about/codeofconduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pt-br/about/codeofconduct/</guid><description>Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.</description></item><item><title>Membros</title><link>/pt-br/about/members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pt-br/about/members/</guid><description>A comunidade InnerSource Commons (ISC) está aberta a todos. Alguns participantes da comunidade vão além e podem ser convidados a se tornarem membros do ISC.</description></item><item><title>Nossos Patrocinadores</title><link>/pt-br/about/sponsors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pt-br/about/sponsors/</guid><description>Nossos Parceiros Bitergia GitHub IBM Microsoft Nossos Apoiadores Adeo Bosch Comcast Fannie Mae Mercedes Benz Red Hat SAP Torne-se um Patrocinador</description></item><item><title>Política de Privacidade</title><link>/pt-br/about/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/pt-br/about/privacy/</guid><description>A InnerSource Commons é uma organização independente e sem fins lucrativos que cria e compartilha conhecimento sobre InnerSource para seus membros.</description></item></channel></rss>