<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>InnerSource Commons</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/</link><description>Recent content on InnerSource Commons</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>ja</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>InnerSource for Project Leaders</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/01/</guid><description>After completing this segment, you will have a better understanding of how InnerSource speeds up product development.</description></item><item><title>Trusted Committerの役割の紹介</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/01/</guid><description>Trusted Committer(TC)の役割は、InnerSourceコミュニティにおける重要な役割の1つです。 Trusted Committerは、重要な技術的決定や、最終的にコントリビューションをゴールまで導くためにコントリビューターのメンタリングを行う、あなたが信頼するコミュニティの人々だと考えてください。 Trusted Committerの役割は、要求が厳しくやりがいがあるものです。 それは単なる独断的なゲートキーパー以上のもので、あらゆるInnerSourceコミュニティの成功に役立ちます。
一般的に、Trusted Committerの役割は、権限ではなく責任によって定義されます。 非常に高いレベルでは、Trusted Committer達はInnerSourceコミュニティと、コミュニティが構築している製品の両方の利益を代表しています。 彼らはコミュニティと製品の両方の健全性に関心があります。 したがって、Trusted Committerとしては、技術指向とコミュニティ指向の両方の責任があります。 次のセクションでは、これらの両方の側面について説明します。</description></item><item><title>インナーソース パターン</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/patterns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/patterns/</guid><description>InnerSource Commons は、インナーソース パターンという形で、コミュニティがお互いの経験を共有し、学ぶための場を提供しています。 インナーソースパターン - InnerSource のベスト プラクティスと呼ばれる特定の形式でまとめられたもので、コンテキストでの理解・評価・適用を容易にします。
ワーキンググループの活動 コミュニティコールやSlackでのディスカッションなど、様々な場面でパターンの特定を促進します。 パターンをレビューし、そのパターンが使用された例を提供することで、コミュニティの成熟を支援しています。 GitHub で企業がパターンを共同開発する場を提供しています インナーソースパターンブックでは最も成熟したパターンを公開しています。 インナーソースパターンマインドマップなどの探索ツールを提供しています。 How to Get Involved もしあなたが既に社内でインナーソースを使っていて、自分の経験を共有したり、新しいパターンを紹介したりして、上記の取り組みに貢献したいとお考えなのであれば、ぜひ本への投稿や、#innersource-patterns チャンネルでのSlack会話への参加をお待ちしています。</description></item><item><title>インナーソース入門</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/getting-started-with-innersource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/getting-started-with-innersource/</guid><description>インナーソースは、閉じた組織におけるオープンソースソフトウェアを開発するための原動力であり、プロジェクトの &amp;ldquo;オープン性&amp;rdquo; を企業内のチームを超えて広げるものです。この本では、オライリーの編集者兼著者である Andy Oram氏が、オープンソース開発を成功させる原則を確認するとともに、PayPal でインナーソースがどのように機能したのかを説明することによって、皆様をインナーソースの世界に導きます。</description></item><item><title>はじめに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/01/</guid><description>InnerSourceのコントリビューター あなたは、あなたの依存する機能を他チームがシステムに追加をする時間が無いために、次のコーディングタスクをブロックされたことはありませんか？ もしかすると、しばらくしてから、その不足している機能を補うために、あなたのプロジェクトで余計な作業をしなければならなかったかも知れません。 このような形で全くブロックされないことは、どんなに素晴らしいことでしょうか？
InnerSourceの原則を組み込んだプロジェクトでは、必要な機能を他のチームが提供するのを待ってブロックされることは決してありません。 もし必要なものが得られないなら、InnerSourceコントリビューターとして行動し、他チームのコードリポジトリに直接あなたが必要な変更を行うことかできます。
コントリビューターの役割は、InnerSourceコミュニティプロジェクトのリポジトリに貢献する人と表されます。 この人はコミュニティの一部の人であるかも知れないし、そうでないかも知れません。 しかし、かなりの数の人にとってコントリビューターとは、単にコミュニティについて知るだけのことから、コミュニティのプロダクトを使用し、コミュニティのメンバーと対話し、そして最終的に貢献を始めることができるという旅のようなものです。 最終的に、そのうち何人かは Trusted Committer(トラステッドコミッター) になるかも知れません。
他の役割との関係 InnerSourceコミュニティにおけるコントリビューターとしてあなたは、 Trusted Committer や Product Owner (プロダクトオーナー) などのInnerSourceの他の役割を担っている人や、おそらく他のコントリビューターとも交流することになります。 まれに、小さな草の根スタイルのプロジェクトでは、Trusted Committerとプロダクトオーナーなどの役割は同じ人が行うことができます。</description></item><item><title>はじめに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/01/</guid><description>このラーニングパスは、InnerSourceの紹介にあたるものです。 InnerSourceは、企業内のソフトウェア開発にオープンソースの実践と原則を適用したものです。 InnerSourceソフトウェアは、会社としてはプロプライエタリなものとなりますが、内部にはオープンで、誰もが利用したり貢献したりできるようになります。 この方法は、広範かつ効果的なコラボレーション、内部の多くのステークホルダーからの変化する要求に、迅速かつ軽快に対応することを可能とします。
このラーニングパスでは、InnerSourceを適用する良い候補となる状況を、どのように認識するかについて学びます。 私たちは、これらの状況でどのようにInnerSourceが活用できるか概略を示します。 それにより、あなたはInnerSourceについて議論する際の共通用語に詳しくなるでしょう。 私たちはまた、InnerSourceの基礎となる主要な原則と、それが効果的に適用された時に得られる効果を列挙します。</description></item><item><title>はじめに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/01/</guid><description>こんにちは、中間管理職やプロダクトオーナー、プログラムマネージャーの皆さん。 もっと幸せで効果的なチームをリードしたいと思いますか？ 報告地獄に閉じ込められた記録係よりもリーダーになりたいですか？ 私の会社にInnerSourceのプロセスを導入したことで、約80%が割り込み駆動型開発だった複数の大規模システムのリファクタリングをすることができました。 そして私たちは皆、その環境を管理すること、ましてや開発することが、いかに難しいかを知っています。
InnerSourceプロセスを通じて、私たちは数十年積み残していた内部残件を1年足らずで削減もしました。 InnerSouceの重要な要素はオープンであることです。 これは、ほとんどの企業のチームが陥っているサイロ化を破壊します。 これを実現可能にして、数え切れない管理や開発者の時間を節約する、基本的なInnerSourceの手法について説明します。
こんにちは。Sliona Bonewald です。PayPalでディレクターをしています。 InnerSourceプロセスでは、40以上のチームと1500人以上のスタッフのトレーニングに成功しました。 また、InnerSourceコモンズにも参加して定期的に講演しています。 是非ご参加ください。 innersourcecommons.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource and Agile</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/02/</guid><description>You want to improve your product and deliver faster to customers. You want to make stakeholders happy.</description></item><item><title>InnerSourceコントリビューターになる</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/02/</guid><description>InnerSourceのコントリビューターは、通常のチームの境界外で活動し、組織のサイロを横断するリンクになります。 そのため、彼らはこの作業をより効果あるものにするための、いくつかの共通の方法を意識する必要があります。
マインドセットの共有 それでは - あなたはチームの製品に、新しい機能を実装しています。 この機能を動作させるためには、いくつかの機能が必要です。 実装に直ぐに取り掛かる代わりに、少し落ち着いて考えます：この機能は一般的な課題なのだろうか？ それは、あなたの組織の他のチームが共有するビジネスドメインで同じように直面しているものなのか？ この機能は、あなたのプロジェクトのドメインと直交するものなのか？ もし当てはまる場合、自分のチームを超えて見渡して：あなたのニーズにフィットするために利用したり改善できる共通のソリューションがあるのか？ あるべきなのか？
ソリューションを共有するメリット アフリカには、 &amp;#8220;早く行きたいなら一人で行きなさい。遠くに行きたいなら一緒に行きなさい&amp;#8221;　という諺があります。これは、ソフトウェア開発チームにも同じです。</description></item><item><title>InnerSourceによって解決される課題とは？</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/02/</guid><description>InnerSourceは、企業の組織構造やその立場に関係なく、誰もがコードを再利用したりコラボレーションすることを推奨し、それに報いることができるものです。 このアプローチは、従来の組織に見られるアイデアや成果物を企業組織の階層やサイロの中に閉じ込めておくものとは異なるものです。 この考えについて実例をあげて見ていきましょう。
同じ会社にある二つのチームが、別々のソフトウェア部品を提供する時、片方のチームのソフトウェアが、もう一方のチームのソフトウェアに依存する状況を想像してください。 もう少し具体的にユーザエクスペリエンスを例にすると、表示用データを取得するAPIに依存するサービスがあります。 このような状況は、一つのチームが作成するソフトウェアが、数十人、数百人の利用される大企業では一般的なことです。
利用側のチームが多くの機能を必要とした時、提供側のチームは通常、どの機能から開発を進めるかを決めるために、ある種の要件や優先度付けを行うプロセスを持っています。 すぐに作業に取り掛かるため優先度が付けられていなかった重要な機能のリクエストのために、利用側のチームは通常、次に示す3つのオプションから一つを選択することになると思いますが、それぞれ欠点があります。
静観： 利用側のチームは何もせずにリスエストされた機能が無いために足を引っ張られるかもしれません。 このオプションは、利用側の作業を最小限にすることができます。 機能リクエストの効果に依存しているかもしれませんが、もしかすると待つだけで良いかもしれません。 しかし、これは苦痛を伴うかもしれません。要求された機能がいつまでたっても提供されない場合は、特に大きな苦痛を伴います。
回避策： 利用側のチームが待ちたくない時は、利用側が要求する機能が足りない部分を補うために、別の場所で追加作業をするかもしれません。 この追加作業は、利用側のプロジェクトの変更となるかもしれません。 あるいは、利用側のチームは彼らのニーズを満たし、開発チームの全部もしくは一部の仕様を置き換える新しいプロジェクトを作成するかもしれません（コード/プロジェクトの複製）。 こうした方法は、利用側のチームが要求する機能を自分たちの努力だけで手に入れることができます。とはいえ、これには幾つかの欠点があります。</description></item><item><title>インナーソース パターンブック</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/innersource-patterns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/innersource-patterns/</guid><description>インナーソース パターンとは、特定の形式で成文化された、文脈の理解、評価、および適用を容易にするインナーソースのベストプラクティスです。 この本には、InnerSource Commonsによって収集された、最も成熟したパターンが含まれています。</description></item><item><title>製品品質の確保</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/02/</guid><description>まず、Trusted Committerの役割に最もよく関連する責任、製品の品質を確保することから始めましょう。
InnerSourceのコミュニティでTrusted Committerたちは、すべての技術関連の意思決定、特に製品品質に関する意思決定の 権利を持っています 。 権利を持つということは、適切な決定が確実に実行されるようにする必要があるということを意味します。 これには、コミュニティ内外で意思疎通を図り、必要に応じてこれらの決定を支持することが含まれます。 しかし、Trusted Committerは、必ずしも技術関連の決定をすべて自分で行ったり、それを実装するためのすべての作業を行うわけではありません。
Trusted Committerの仕事は、彼らのコミュニティの品質基準を伝え、明確にし、 コントリビューター が理解でき、実行可能な形にそれらを策定することです。 これにはもちろん書面による文書も含まれますが、Trusted Committerがこれらの品質基準を伝える最も効果的な方法は、例示によるものです。 私たちは、InnerSourceコミュニティが開発をまとめる方法だけでなく、彼らが作成するソフトウェアの品質においても、従来のソフトウェア開発プロジェクトと差別化を図ることは価値ある目標であると考えています。 ソフトウェア品質の高さは、InnerSourceコミュニティのユーザとその管理者の信頼を確立し維持するために不可欠なものです。 私たちは皆、1つの悪いリリースが、この信頼を一瞬にして打ち砕いてしまうことを知っています。</description></item><item><title>中間管理職でいることの難しさ</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/02/</guid><description>まずは、プロダクトオーナーや中間管理職の人に話を聞いてみることから始めましょう。 ツライですね、統計からもわかります。 Googleで"中間管理職"と検索してみても、ほとんどの結果はそれが如何に大変かについてです。
これが統計情報になります。 中間管理職の皆さんは、上司や部下よりもうつ病や不安を抱えている割合が高いです。 半数以上が常に不安を感じていると言うことです。 Harvard Business Reviewが32万人以上の従業員を対象に実施した調査によると、中間管理職の仕事の満足度は下位5%だということが明らかになりました。痛い！
私が見つけた共通の不満を意訳すると、中間管理職は上層部のビジョン作成には関わらず、責任を取らされることがよくあります。 リーダーシップ能力を必要とする人にとって、これほどモチベーションが下がるものを思いつきません。
いくつかの調査を読んでわかった不満のトップ5は、次の通りです。
最初は、混沌と機能不全に陥ったプロダクトチームを引き継ぐことです。
2番目は、柔軟性がなく、創造性を発揮する余地がほとんどないことです。多くの場合、これには明確な道筋が含まれていません。</description></item><item><title>InnerSource and Planning</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/03/</guid><description>Planning plays a role in InnerSource in two important situations:
Contributing teams need to understand that working on upstream code typically does need more time than making comparable changes to their own codebase that they are well familiar with.</description></item><item><title>InnerSourceのプロセスに組込まれている主なメリット</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/03/</guid><description>InnerSourceコモンズ では、オープンソースで学んだ オープン の概念について説明し、また、企業の中で私たちが知っていることや学んだことを再利用する方法について説明します。 それでは、マネージャーの視点からいくつか順を追っていきましょう。ディレクターとして、そしてPayPalではプロダクトオーナーと呼ぶプロダクトマネージャーとして、私にどのようなメリットをもたらしたかを説明します。
最初は、 オープンコード です。 オープンコードとは、何でしょうか？基本的には、コードが企業全体から見えるということ、そして、他の開発者が他のコードベースにプルリクエストを送信して受け入れるプロセスがあるということです。 さらに理解を深めるために、詳細については Trusted Committer と、コントリビューションアグリーメントに関する記事を参照してください。
マネージャーにとってのオープンコードとは、他チームのコードベースでバグ修正や機能実装されるのを待ったり、エスカレーションしたりする必要がなくなることを意味しています。 実装や計画を、より効果的に始めることができます。 多くの場合、あなたのチームの問題(または機能)は、他チームの最優先事項ではないかもしれません。 そのチームにアクセスするために、上層部へのエスカレーションや政治に頼る必要はもうありません。 代わりに、あなたのチームで優先順位を決定し、他者への依存を減らすことができる、より多くの力を手に入れます。 知識の習得までに、より時間がかかる場合もあります。しかし、それが常にボトルネックとなっているチームでは、何年も放置されているストーリーを、他チームのバックログから取り出すことができます。</description></item><item><title>Understanding the InnerSource Checklist</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/understanding-the-innersource-checklist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/understanding-the-innersource-checklist/</guid><description>Silona Bonewald氏が、オープンソースからの教訓を適用することによって、インナーソースのイニシアチブがあなたの会社が社内でソフトウェアを開発するのにどのように役立つのかを解説します。このチェックリストは、それが会社全体であるかどうか、または1つのチームのために、インナーソースのアプローチを使用してソフトウェアを生成するために必要な様々なガイダンスとなります。</description></item><item><title>コミュニティの健全性維持</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/03/</guid><description>本章の導入で Trusted Committerには技術指向とコミュニティ指向の両方の責任があることを指摘しました。 それは、コードとコードの健全性だけに注目するだけでは不十分だということです。 長期的な成功を確実にするために、Trusted Committerはソフトウェアを構築するコミュニティの健全性維持にも努めるべきです。 そのためには、製品の品質を確保することと健全なコミュニティを育てることの間で、バランスを取る必要があります。
健全なコミュニティとはどのようなものでしょうか？ 簡単に言うと、健全なコミュニティでは、 コントリビューター はソフトウェア開発にほとんどの時間を費やすことができ、能力を高めることができます。 その結果、健全なコミュニティは、継続して成長することになります。
なぜ、 コントリビューター はコミュニティに参加して留まるのでしょうか？ コミュニティの目的や使命に賛同しているため、そうする人達がいます。 この目的を明確にして推進することが、Trusted Committerの仕事です。 この重要性は、認識されていないことが多いが、コミュニティとそのプロダクトをマーケティングすることは本当に重要です。</description></item><item><title>コントリビューターの心構え</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/03/</guid><description>前のセグメントでは、あなたがコンポーネントを再利用してコントリビューターとして活動するようになるかの理由を説明しました。 この記事では、ホストチームのコードベースにあなたの変更をうまく提供する方法のベストプラクティスを共有します。
ホストチームに貢献しようとしているInnerSouceのコントリビューターは、基本的には彼らの家のゲストです。 一般的に、良いゲストは決められた方法で行動することが期待されています。
ドアをノックする
ハウスルールを予測して従う
家のオーナーではないことを理解し、それに応じた行動をする
これらの期待は、どのようにInnerSourceのプロジェクトに適用されるのでしょうか？
入る 隣人を訪ねるとき、たとえドアが開いていても、ノックしたりドアベルを鳴らしたりせずに彼らの家に入ることはないでしょう。 同様に、InnerSourceにおいても、訪問者としてどのコードリポジトリに対しても直接コミットすることはできません（または招待されません）。
代わりに、コードベースに変更を加えた後、それらをプルリクエストとして送信します。 大規模な変更を行うことや、隣人の家の改善を考えたりしないのと同様に、InnerSourceではプロジェクトのコラボレーション・ガイドラインを予測し、それに従うことになります。 今度は、ホストがあなたに方法を示します - InnerSourceでは、既存のTrusted Committer達がゲストを指導するために時間を費やしていることと解釈します。</description></item><item><title>どのようにInnerSourceは機能するのか？</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/03/</guid><description>AチームがBチームから提供されるソフトウェアを利用する場合を例に考えてみましょう。 AチームはBチームに機能追加のリクエストを送ります、でもBチームはそれを期限内に実装してAチームにリリースすることはできません。 InnerSourceでは、もしAチームがこの要求機能を得ることができない場合、代わりにプルリクエストを送信します。 それは、AチームはBチームのソフトウェアに直接機能を実装してプルリクエストを送付することを意味します。 チームBは連携して送付されたコードをレビューして受け入れます。
この例において、チームAは ゲスト チーム、チームBは ホスト チームと呼ばれます。 ゲスト や ホスト の用語は、自宅にお客を招くような感覚で使われています。 この状況では、殆どの人は良いホストとなること期待しています。 彼らはゲストの到着を見越して、物事が整理整頓されていることを保証します。 訪問者は、ドアのところで迎えられて中に招かれます。</description></item><item><title>State of InnerSource Survey 2024</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2024/</guid><description>Report of the 2024 State of InnerSource Survey</description></item><item><title>State of InnerSource Survey 2023</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2022-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2022-2023/</guid><description>Report of the 2022-2023 State of InnerSource Survey</description></item><item><title>2021年度インナーソース年次調査報告書</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2021/</guid><description>2021年度 State of InnerSource サーベイにかかる報告書</description></item><item><title>2020年度インナーソース年次調査報告書</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2020/</guid><description>2020年度 State of InnerSource サーベイにかかる報告書</description></item><item><title>2016年度インナーソース年次調査報告書</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/research/state-of-innersource-survey-2016/</guid><description>2016年度 State of InnerSource サーベイにかかる報告書</description></item><item><title>Adopting InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/adopting-innersource-principles-and-case-studies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/adopting-innersource-principles-and-case-studies/</guid><description>Danese Cooper氏と Klaas-Jan Stol氏が、インナーソースがあなたの組織にとってどのように有用であるかを示すために、様々な企業でのケーススタディを紹介します。ケーススタディでは、これまでの進捗状況やメリットまたは負の影響と一緒に、インナーソースプロジェクトを開始することの難しさを率直に議論しています。</description></item><item><title>InnerSource and Negotiation Skills</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/04/</guid><description>Coding and negotiation? You may ask yourself how these two go together. In particular for InnerSource host teams it helps to have a few stumbling blocks in mind when it comes to change negotiation.</description></item><item><title>InnerSourceの効果とは？</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/04/</guid><description>InnerSourceによるコラボレーションには、多くの効果があります。 InnerSourceは、ゲストチームが長期メンテナンスの負担をせず、 彼らが必要な時に機能要求を手に入れる ためのスケーラブルな戦略を企業に提供します。 ゲストチームの時間を、他の人たちが利用できるコードに投入することが、会社全体としての勝利へとつながります。
この結果はInnerSourceの優れた効果であると同時に、定常的にInnerSourceのコントリビューションを受け取るホストにも多くの効果があります。 InnerSourceのプロセスの一部には、ホストチームのプロダクトオーナーが、コントリビューションされた機能が正しくかつ望まれたものであることに、最初から同意していることを思い出してください。 InnerSourceは、それを利用する人達のために 良いプロダクトを作るための支援 をホストチームが受け取ることを可能にします!
InnerSourceはホストチームにスケーラブルな戦略を提供し 、多くの利用者たちからの、さまざまな機能要求に応えてゆくことが可能となります。 ホストチームのフルタイムメンバーの対応力が固定されているとした場合、時として、その利用者たちのビジネスロードマップの組み合せが、ホストチームの製品で非常に（または理不尽に）大量の作業を必要とすることにつながる可能性があります。 InnerSourceなしでは、こうした状況は、リーダーにエスカレーションされた多くの機能要求に対処する、過労とストレスに満ちたチームを簡単に生みだすことにつながります。</description></item><item><title>コミュニティメンバーのレベル向上</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/04/</guid><description>InnerSourceコミュニティへの参加には連続性があります。 コミュニティについて知らない人達がいます。 新規参加者 は、コミュニティとその製品に関心があるかもしれませんが、まだそれを使用していません。 消費者 は、ソフトウェアを使用しますが、コントリビューションしていない可能性があります。 次に、少なくとも一つはコントリビューションをしている コントリビューター がおり、最後にソフトウェアとコミュニティの両方に責任を持つ_Trusted Committer_ がいます。 Trusted Committerとしては、この連続性に沿う形で個人を動かし、コントリビューションする能力を高めていく責任があります。 この意味で、Trusted Committerは、コミュニティにおけるフォースマルチプライヤーとして機能します。</description></item><item><title>コントリビューションの仕組み</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/04/</guid><description>他のチームのプロジェクト/リポジトリに貢献を始める準備はできていますか？ マネージメント層へのエスカレーションではなく、コラボレーションでブロッカーを減らすことを楽しみにしていますか？ このセクションでは、InnerSourceに貢献する際に覚えておくべき落とし穴に焦点を当て、実践的なアドバイスを提供します。 これにより、あなたとホストチームが可能な限り快適な経験をすることを可能とし、より多くのコントリビューションと素晴らしいコラボレーションをするための基礎を築きます。
この記事は、あなたがおそらく経験する次の3つのステップに分かれています。
コントリビューションの機会を求め、それに取り組む準備をする
実際にコントリビューションするものを作成する
ギフトをキレイにして包み、ホストチームに提供する
もし、あなたの貢献がより大きければ、共通の目標に向かって反復しながら、これらのステップ（の一部）を繰り返し実行する可能性があります。 そうすることで、すべてのことがより自然に感じられるようになる可能性が非常に高くなるでしょうし、おそらく、以前に何か他のことをしていた理由を不思議に思うかもしれません。
取り組む準備をする リードタイム 一つの重要な違いは、ターンアラウンドタイムです。 初めてコントリビューションする時はいつも、あなたは新しい（ホスト）チームに参加する事になります。 その結果、あなたは彼らのコードベース、使用している技術、そして彼らの好む開発環境（テストフレームワークやビルドシステムを想像してください）について知る必要があります。 この種のツールが標準化されている場合でも、各チームはいくらかの個性があります。 技術的な側面に加えて、コミュニケーション方法の違いに直面することもあるかもしれません（コードレビューを想像してください）。 しばらくして戻ってきたときには、チームのやり方やメンバーが変わっているかも知れません。 しばらく会っていなかった友人を訪ねてキャッチアップする時と同じように時間をかけてください。</description></item><item><title>新しい役割と責任</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/04/</guid><description>InnerSourceのリーダーには、新しい役割と責任が伴います。 その最初の1つが、TCをサポートすることです。TCは、 Trusted Committer です。 あなたが最初に行うことの1つは、おそらく、TCが誰になるかの選抜を支援し、彼らの仕事をサポートすることです。 もし、TCの役割について詳しく知りたければ、 Trusted Committer の章を参照してください。
彼らは、あなたのコードベースのゲートキーパーです。 通常、彼らはコードレビューを得意とし、コードベースのアーキテクチャを深く理解しているリード開発者です。 彼らにはあなたのサポートが必要です。 他チームとのコラボレーションにおいても、彼らは重要です。 見積りやインテグレーションでは、あなたの右腕となるでしょう。彼らをサポートするのを忘れないでください。 彼らにはいくつかとても大変な新しい責任があり、 コントリビューションするチーム を支援するために指導が必要になるかもしれません。 開発者が交渉方法を教えられることはあまりありません。 私は、 Getting to Yes という本を、彼らと一緒に使うことをお勧めします。</description></item><item><title>InnerSourceのコントリビューターになるメリット</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/05/</guid><description>コントリビューターはInnerSourceプロジェクトの生命線です。 InnerSourceプロジェクトとして実行されるすべてのプロジェクトには、開発チームを当初の創設者の枠を超えて拡大し、そのプロジェクトのユーザー（時に企業では顧客とも呼ばれる）間でさらなる協力者の可能性を利用するという見込みと究極の目標の両方があります。
しかし、個々の開発者がマネージャの指示を受けていないプロジェクトに対して時間を費やす動機は何でしょうか？ マネージャが、開発者に対して100%自分の管理下にないプロジェクトの改善に時間を作る動機となるものは何でしょうか？
個人の動機 最も自明な動機は、初期のコントリビューターをオープンソースに引き込むことです。
あなたが長い間回避してきた迷惑なバグを覚えていますか？ これらの回避策のメンテナンスに費やす時間とエネルギーは？ アップストリームチームが将来その問題を修正するのを待たずに、先に自分で問題を修正できるとしたらどうでしょうか？ この「自分の手で問題を解決する」状況が初めてのコントリビューターは、自分のコードベースの回避策の数を減らすために、日々の作業に依存するプロジェクトの問題を修正することから始めることがよくあります。
独自の回避策を維持するのではなく、修正を作成してコントリビューションするかどうかを決めるときには、そのコントリビューションが独自の変更の品質にもたらすメリットについて考えてください。 単独で作業する代わりに、アップストリームプロジェクトで作業する人は、あなたのソリューションをレビューするだけでなく改善することもできます。 サポートと指導を受けることで、開発作業が大幅にスピードアップします。
他の人と多くの時間を過ごすことは、時間が経つにつれて、チームがどのように機能するか、どのように組織化されるか、どのようなツールを用いてプロジェクトを構築しているかを学ぶことを意味します。 新しいライブラリやビルドシステムについて読むだけではなく、それを自分のプロジェクトに導入する前に実践的な経験を積むことができるので、多くの場合、あなた自身のプロジェクトもその経験から恩恵を受けることになるでしょう。 複数のコアプロジェクトに取り組むことは、課題に対するベストプラクティスとソリューションを引き出す、より大きなエコシステムに晒されることを意味します。</description></item><item><title>InnerSourceの原則</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/05/</guid><description>会社、チーム、プロジェクト、そして個人はそれぞれ異ります。 ですので、InnerSourceのコンセプトが実際に機能する正しい方法は、ある状況と他の状況とで異なるものになるでしょう。 しかし、InnerSourceの成功例の根底には4つの原則があります。 これらの原則は、オープンソースプロジェクトの成功からインスピレーションを得ており、InnerSourceが前に説明したような効果を得るために必要なものです。
これらの原則は次の通りです：
オープン性
透明性
優先的なメンターシップ
自発的なコードコントリビューション
それでは、それぞれの原則について詳細を見ていきましょう。
オープン性 オープンなプロジェクトを構成することで、摩擦のないコントリビューションが可能となります。 プロジェクトは、リポジトリのトップに置かれる README.md ファイルと CONTRIBUTING.</description></item><item><title>Options for Shared Ownership</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/05/</guid><description>"If everyone owns it, nobody is accountable." Traditional organizations prefer to have a single point of contact in case of issues.</description></item><item><title>インナーソースプロジェクトの管理方法</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/managing-innersource-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/books/managing-innersource-projects/</guid><description>インナーソースのプロジェクトを管理する方法とは? この本では、Daniel Izquierdo氏と José Manrique López氏が、基本的なインフラストラクチャとに、企業にインナーソースの方法論を導入する際に有用であるメトリックを説明しています。</description></item><item><title>参入障壁を下げる</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/05/</guid><description>InnerSourceコミュニティでコントリビューションを求めることは、いくつかの理由からオープンソースコミュニティよりも困難です。
InnerSourceコミュニティでは、潜在的な コントリビューター の数が少ない。
コントリビューターは、勤務時間内にコントリビューションしたいと考えるため、時間の制約が大きくなる。
InnerSourceでの作業は、コントリビューターの正式な目標管理の一部に必ずなるとは限らないため、InnerSourceの作業に費やす時間が目標達成を損なうように見える場合がある。
そのため、Trusted Committerにとって、 コントリビューター のオンボーディングやコントリビューション作成のプロセスを、できるだけスムーズにすることが重要となります。 役立つことがいくつかあります。
各コードリポジトリに、適切な README.md を用意する。 適切な README.</description></item><item><title>要約と要点</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/05/</guid><description>この記事で説明した内容をまとめるために、簡単な振り返りをしたいと思います。
まずは、労りましょう。中間管理職は大変です。
私たちが話した主なメリットのいくつかについても説明していきます。 私たちは、InnerSourceがボトルネックを取り除くのにどのように役立つかについて、さまざまな方法を話しました。 また、中間管理職になることで、より多くの責任とより多くの統制力を得る方法について話しました。
また、同僚とより多くコラボレーションすることで、より少ないリソースでより多くの成果を達成でき、その結果、こうした冗長性に実際に対処することができます。 オープンプロセスは、おそらく以前得ていたよりも多くの信用を、あなたの仕事に与えることを意味しています。 これらの計画プロセスを実行して公開することで、すべてがより明確になるため、政治的問題を少なくすることができます。
そして最後に、新しい Trusted Committer をサポートするなどの新しい役割と責任があります。 彼らは、本当にあなたの助けを必要とするでしょう。 また、他のプロダクトオーナーと協力することで、より多くの作業をより短期間で行うことができます。 新しいドキュメントに関しては多くの時間を費やす必要がありますが、それでも大丈夫です。なぜなら、より多くの信用を得られるからです。</description></item><item><title>Relation to Open Source</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/project-leader/06/</guid><description>InnerSource is the application of Open Source collaboration best practices inside of the confines of corporations.</description></item><item><title>おわりに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/06/</guid><description>InnerSourceラーニングパス、コントリビューターセグメントをご覧いただきありがとうございます。 このセクションでは、InnerSourceプロジェクトの生命線となる、コントリビューターの役割について学びました。 コントリビューターは、コンポーネント所有者の外側にあり、プロジェクトに追加の貴重な情報をもたらします。
このセクションでは、コントリビューションする機会を見つけてコントリビューターになる方法について学びました。 そのような機会を見つけたり作ったりするのに必要な考え方や習慣について見直しました。 また、その役割の心構えと、コントリビューションを成功に導く可能性のあるアプローチについても説明しました。
正しい考え方や、習慣、心構えをしていても、コントリビューションの成功を妨げるものがいくつかあります。そのため、それらの要点について、詳細を説明しました。
最後に、あなたのチームメイトや組織のさまざまなレベルを説得することが難しい場合があるため、このプロセスを簡単にするために、さまざまな観点からコントリビューションのメリットを詳細に説明しました。
あなたが記事を読んだりビデオを見たりすることを楽しみ、InnerSourceと良いコントリビューターになることに向けた旅のために、興味深く新しい洞察をいくつか得ることができることを願っています。
もし、まだそうしていない場合は、InnerSourceラーニングパス( http://innersourcecommons.org/learningpath/ )で、InnerSouceの他の側面ついて、さらに学ぶことをお勧めします。
オンラインのInnerSourceグループ InnerSourceコモンズ をチェックすることをお勧めします。自由に議論に参加して、あなたの組織で学んだり経験したことを共有してください。</description></item><item><title>おわりに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/06/</guid><description>このラーニングパスでは、InnerSourceの紹介をしました。 InnerSourceは、企業内のソフトウェア開発にオープンソースのベストプラクティスと原則を適用したものです。 これは、提供側のチームが必要な機能要件を提供することができない時に、利用者に追加オプションを提供するものです。 InnerSourceの成功には、 ホストチーム の プロダクトオーナー と Trusted Committer 、そして ゲストチーム の コントリビューター が関わります。 効果的に行うと、InnerSourceは両方の参加チームに多くの効果をもたらします。 効果的なInnerSource実施の主要な原則は、 自発的なコードコントリビューション と 優先的なメンターシップ です。</description></item><item><title>おわりに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/06/</guid><description>是非、 innersourcecommon.org まで連絡をいただき、オンラインでご参加ください。 私たちは、80以上の企業が参加するとてもアクティブなコミュニティです。 それらの多くは、Fortune 500の企業です。
他のビデオをまだ視聴されていなければ、是非ご覧ください。 そこには、InnerSourceのプロセスをあなたの会社に実装するために必要な最初のいくつかのステップが含まれています。 また、https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer[Trusted Committer] などの役割や、あなたの最初のコントリビューションの合意形成のような、いくつかの文書についても説明しています。
もしよろしければ、私の本をご覧ください。 innersourcecommons.org/checklist から入手してください。 この本の後ろの部分には、プロダクトオーナーの皆さんが実行すべきことがたくさんあります。 innersourcecommons.</description></item><item><title>コミュニティのニーズを提唱する</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/06/</guid><description>InnerSourceコミュニティは企業内に存在するため、オープンソースコミュニティより制約があります。 時には、コミュニティとビジネスユニットの利益が相反することがあります。 Trusted Committerは、プロジェクトに対する長期的な視点を持っています。 彼らは、健全なコミュニティが、健全なコードの前提条件であることを理解しています。 これが、多くのInnerSourceコミュニティが 「コードよりコミュニティ(Community over Code)」 をモットーとする Apache Way でモデル化された理由です。 一方でビジネスユニットは、当然ながら、InnerSourceコミュニティにより作成される製品により大きな関心をもちます。 彼らは、短期から中期の業績で利益がでることを好みます。</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/07/</guid><description>To conclude the Introduction segment of the Learning Path, here are some Frequently Asked Questions people have when embarking on their InnerSource journey.</description></item><item><title>Trusted Committerになる</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/07/</guid><description>Trusted Committerの役割は、大変ですがやり甲斐のあるものです。 このラーニングパスに興味があるのであれば、実際にTrsuted Committerになる方法と、自分がそれに適した人物であるかを知りたいと思うかもしれません。
InnerSourceコミュニティは、オープンソースコミュニティと同じ原則に従っており、その一つに実力主義があります。 実力主義において、権力は才能、努力、成果に基づいて個人に与えられます。 つまり、Trusted Committerの役割に伴う権限と特権は、獲得する必要があるものだということです。 オープンソースのもう1つの価値である透明性は、才能、努力、成果をコミュニティ全体に見えるようにするという点でも重要な役割を果たしています。
正式にTrusted Committerになるプロセスは、コミュニティごとに異なり、InnerSourceの行路のどこにいるかに依り、時間とともに進化するかもしれません。 草の根コミュニティでは、創設者がTrusted Committerの役割を担うことが良くあります。 コミュニティが成長するにつれて、またはより大きなコミュニティでは、Trusted Committerは通常、コミュニティの コントリビューター から指名されたり投票されたりします。 しかし、Trusted Committerの役割は、成功のために多大な時間と献身を必要とするため、自発的に引き受けなければなりません。</description></item><item><title>Workbook</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/workbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/contributor/workbook/</guid><description>Video: InnerSource Contributor SEGMENT: Becoming an InnerSource Contributor TIP: More than one answer may be correct in some questions.</description></item><item><title>Workbook</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/workbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/product-owner/workbook/</guid><description>Video: InnerSource Product Owners SEGMENT: How Difficult It Is to Be Middle Management TIP: More than one answer may be correct in some questions.</description></item><item><title>Is InnerSource Right for My Project?</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/08/</guid><description>InnerSource is the application of open source principles to company-internal software development. Done right, it unblocks progress and eases adoption of shared services and modules.</description></item><item><title>おわりに</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/08/</guid><description>ここまでの節では、Trusted Committerの責任について学びました。 これらの責任には、製品の品質確保、コミュニティの健全性の維持、コントリビューションする際の障壁の低減、コミュニティのレベル向上、組織内でのそのニーズの主張などが含まれます。 また、Trusted Committerになる方法と、その役割を果たすために必要なことについても説明しました。 Trusted Committerとして働くことは大変ですが、最終的にはあなたの会社におけるコントリビューションの価値を増幅することになります。
Trusted Committerになるための道を歩むきっかけになればと思います。 また、InnerSourceのイニシアティブを成功させるために、有能なTrusted Committerがいることの重要性と、この役割に必要な権限レベルについて、組織が理解する助けになればと思います。
InnerSourceラーニングパスの他の記事や動画を見て、InnerSourceについて、さらに学んでみることをお勧めします。 そしてもちろん、 InnerSourceコモンズコミュニティ は、あなたをとても歓迎しています。</description></item><item><title>The InnerSource Mentality</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/09/</guid><description>InnerSource helps when there are multiple teams at our company that have a shared need - business or technical.</description></item><item><title>Workbook</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/workbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer/workbook/</guid><description>Video: The Trusted Committer Role in InnerSource SEGMENT: Introduction Question 1. What sentence best describes the motivation for the name “Trusted Committer”?</description></item><item><title>Workbook</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/workbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/learning-path/introduction/workbook/</guid><description>Video: Introduction to InnerSource SEGMENT: What Problems Does InnerSource Solve? TIP: More than one answer may be correct in some questions.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Summit 2025</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2025/</guid><description>🎟️ Get Your Ticket for InnerSource Summit 2025! Join us on Thursday, 13th November 2025 to celebrate 10 years of InnerSource Commons — with events happening across Yokohama 🇯🇵, Berlin 🇩🇪, New York 🇺🇸, and online 🌍!</description></item><item><title>🧭 Choose Your Own InnerSource Adventure - Start Here</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/community/quick-start-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/community/quick-start-guide/</guid><description>Welcome! We understand everyone comes to a new community with different goals and backgrounds. This is a great place to start!</description></item><item><title>Platform Engineering and InnerSource - The Separated Twins Finally Reunited</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-06-11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-06-11/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Sébastien Blanc, from Port, discuss Platform Engineering and InnerSource: The Separated Twins Finally Reunited</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2025-06-new-members/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2025-06-new-members/</guid><description>June 3, 2025
New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation
We are excited to announce our new InnerSource Commons (ISC) Foundation Members: Niall Maher, Shoma Kubo, Arthur Fücher, Yoshitake Kobayashi, Ryo Ashikawa, Fernando Correa, Regina Nkenchor, and Dr.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2025-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2025-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May 22, 2025
InnerSource Commons Foundation Announces New Board of Directors The InnerSource Commons Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of its Board of Directors for the upcoming term.</description></item><item><title>Contributor Journey Optimization</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-05-13/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-05-13/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Guilherme Dellagustin, from SAP, discuss Contributor Journey Optimization</description></item><item><title>InnerSource in China - Past, Present, and Future</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-05-06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-05-06/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Jerry Tan, from COPU, discuss InnerSource in China: Past, Present, and Future</description></item><item><title>Empathetic Engineering and InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-04-29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-04-29/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Brittany Istenes, InnerSource Commons Member, discuss Empathetic Engineering and InnerSource</description></item><item><title>Has InnerSource’s Moment Arrived?</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-04-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-04-22/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear John Mark Walker, founder of Open Source Enterprise Network, discuss if InnerSource’s moment has arrived.</description></item><item><title>The InnerSource and open source virtuous cycle</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-03-25/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-03-25/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Tom Sadler, from the BBC, discuss The InnerSource and open source virtuous cycle</description></item><item><title>InnerSource@DB - A Story About Open Source Practices at Deutsche Bahn</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-03-18/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-03-18/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Carsten Hoffmann, from DB Systel GmbH, discuss InnerSource@DB: A Story About Open Source Practices at Deutsche Bahn</description></item><item><title>Project Fleming - An Open Source Discovery Tool</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-02-18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-02-18/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Dr. Christian DeFeo and Ben Butcher, from Shell, discuss Project Fleming: An Open Source Discovery Tool</description></item><item><title>The 10 Dysfunctions of a Company Culture</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-02-04/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-02-04/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Sean Lemson, from Motivated Outcomes, discuss The 10 Dysfunctions of a Company Culture</description></item><item><title>Engineering Corporate Communities - approach, results, and perspectives</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-01-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-01-21/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Alexandre Quach, from Komyu, discuss Engineering Corporate Communities : approach, results, and perspectives.</description></item><item><title>Ways DevRel skills could save your internal contributor community</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-01-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2025-01-14/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Ana Jiménez Santamaría, The Linux Foundation - TODO Group and Developer Relations Foundation, discuss Ways DevRel skills could save your internal contributor community</description></item><item><title>Tax Compliance for Collaborative Software Engineering - Microsoft’s 30 Billion Dollar Problem</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-12-10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-12-10/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Michael Dorner and Dr. Oliver Treidler, from Kolabri, discuss Tax Compliance for Collaborative Software Engineering - Microsoft’s 30 Billion Dollar Problem.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Hackathon - Fun and safe approach to get started</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-12-03/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-12-03/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear Shanmugapriya Manoharan, from IKEA, discuss the InnerSource Hackathon: a Fun and safe approach to get started</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Summit 2024</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2024/</guid><description>Registrations are Now Open 20th &amp;amp; 21st November 2024 - online Join us at the world&amp;rsquo;s leading gathering of InnerSource practitioners.</description></item><item><title>Building Sustainable Internal Developer Platforms with InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-10-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-10-22/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear David Grizzanti, from The New York Times, discuss Building Sustainable Internal Developer Platforms with InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>Promoting InnerSource Practices with an Internal Developer Platform</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-10-08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-10-08/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear from Vincent Caldeira (Red Hat), Clemens Jütte (Humanitec), Luiz Fernando Almeida de Oliveira (Red Hat), as they discuss Promoting InnerSource Practices with an Internal Developer Platform.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with InnerSource Consultations</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-10-01/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-10-01/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear from Gale McCommons &amp;amp; Anusha Pavuluri, from Comcast, as they discuss Getting Started with InnerSource Consultations.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource as one step towards Open Source</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-09-17/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-09-17/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear from Isabel Drost-Fromm, from Europace AG/ InnerSource Commons Foundation, on how to utilize InnerSource as one step towards Open Source.</description></item><item><title>The A,B,Cs of InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-08-13/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-08-13/</guid><description>In this community call we will hear from three senior Members of the InnerSource Commons Foundation.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons AMA (Ask Me Anything)</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-06-20/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-06-20/</guid><description>Join us for an Ask Me Anything session with Georg Grütter and Dr. Wolfgang Gehring. Bring all your questions!</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons AMA (Ask Me Anything)</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-06-11/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-06-11/</guid><description>Join us for an Ask Me Anything session with Matt Cobby and Guilherme Dellagustin. Bring all your questions!</description></item><item><title>State of InnerSource 2024</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-05-23/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-05-23/</guid><description>Join us for our State of InnerSource 2024 Call, where Clare Dillon, from University of Galway, Ireland, will take us on a deep dive of this year&amp;rsquo;s results.</description></item><item><title>Insightful Learning - InnerSource Dojo Way</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-05-21/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-05-21/</guid><description>Unpack the InnerSource Dojo model which led to generating over $4M annually in fresh revenue streams through a strategic Kubernetes initiative.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2024-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2024-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May 15, 2024
The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of the Board for the coming year.</description></item><item><title>Mastering Open Source - Balancing the Code Supply Chain, IP, and Legal Considerations</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-04-30/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-04-30/</guid><description>In this talk, we will explore the delicate balance between the benefits of open sourcing code and the need to protect your company&amp;rsquo;s valuable intellectual property.</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2024-04-new-members/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2024-04-new-members/</guid><description>April 26 2024
We are delighted to announce our new InnerSource Commons (ISC) Foundation Members: Addie Girouard, Brittany Istenes, Chan Voong, Jeff Bailey, Justin Gosses, Thomas Froment and Willem Jiang.</description></item><item><title>Transforming MLOps Culture with InnerSource Principles</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-04-18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-04-18/</guid><description>In this talk, Mishari Muqbil explores how InnerSource principles like collaboration, transparency, and meritocracy can revolutionize MLOps.</description></item><item><title>Defending the Sports Metaphor - An InnerSource Primer</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-03-26/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-03-26/</guid><description>This talk will explore the relationship (or lack-thereof) between InnerSource and Sports to humorously show how the analogies might have utility in the world of software development.</description></item><item><title>Untangling InnerSource - Weaving Collaboration into the Fabric of Your Organisation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-03-19/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-03-19/</guid><description>In this talk, we will explore the intricate dynamics of InnerSource adoption within organisations, likening its structure to a spider&amp;rsquo;s web.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Product Architecture - Lessons Learned from Applying Conway’s Law</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-02-27/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-02-27/</guid><description>This talk will look at the &amp;ldquo;Cross-Product Architecture&amp;rdquo; collaboration model which some consider SAP&amp;rsquo;s largest InnerSource project involving 3,000+ architects and experts across numerous organizations.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource and APIs</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-02-20/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-02-20/</guid><description>This talk will serve as an open discussion for the community of the InnerSource Commons on how to effectively bring together APIs as a way to produce software and have clear communication channels across teams, all with the goal of allowing high API reuse and high autonomy for all teams.</description></item><item><title>Managing InnerSource Projects</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-01-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-01-30/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Yuki Hattori, from GitHub, tell us how he manages InnerSource projects that enables individuals to contribute their expertise, fosters innovation, and strengthens the overall development process within the organization.</description></item><item><title>Effective InnerSource; Strategies for Resource-Constrained Teams</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-01-23/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2024-01-23/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Jeff Bailey tell us how he uses strategies for resource-constrained teams for Effective InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons End of Year Call</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-12-12/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-12-12/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to discuss all that has happened in 2023; celebrate all the wins and look at the learnings.</description></item><item><title>Building an InnerSource Culture of Trust on the Path to Open Source</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-12-05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-12-05/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Brian Proffitt, from Red Hat, discuss how to build an InnerSource culture of trust on the path to open source.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Summit 2023</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2023/</guid><description>Registrations are Now Open 15th &amp;amp; 16th November 2023 - online Join us at the world&amp;rsquo;s leading gathering of InnerSource practitioners.</description></item><item><title>Getting Ready for State of InnerSource 2024</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-10-25/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-10-25/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Clare Dillon, from University of Galway, discuss getting ready for State of InnerSource 2024.</description></item><item><title>Leveraging Special Interest Groups to expand your enterprise InnerSource initiative</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-10-10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-10-10/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Brittany Istenes, from Fannie Mae, discuss the importance of leveraging Special Interest Groups to expand your enterprise InnerSource initiative.</description></item><item><title>Starting with a Blank Slate - Building Your InnerSource Program From the Ground Up</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-09-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-09-19/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Katie Schueths, from Analog Devices, discuss Starting with a Blank Slate - Building Your InnerSource Program From the Ground Up</description></item><item><title>Improving Engineering Collaboration across the Singapore Government through Innersource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-09-13/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-09-13/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Hunter Nield, from Govtech, discuss Improving Engineering Collaboration across the Singapore Government through Innersource</description></item><item><title>Russell Rutledge appointed as new Executive Director of InnerSource Commons</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2023-08-new-executive-director/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2023-08-new-executive-director/</guid><description>August 2023
The InnerSource Commons Foundation (ISC), the world’s foremost community for InnerSource practitioners, today announced Russell Rutledge as its Executive Director.</description></item><item><title>How InnerSource enabled the creation of watsonx.ai</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-07-06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-07-06/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Bill Higgins, from IBM, discuss How InnerSource enabled the creation of watsonx.</description></item><item><title>How the Process Management Standards for Open Source Compliance and Security Impact InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-07-05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-07-05/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Shane Coughlan from OpenChain Project at The Linux Foundation discuss how the Process Management Standards for Open Source Compliance and Security Impact InnerSource</description></item><item><title>Cultural crosswires - how to communicate effectively and still be misunderstood</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-06-28/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-06-28/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Mishari Muqbil from Zymple discuss Cultural Crosswires - how to communicate effectively and still be misunderstood!</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2023-06-new-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2023-06-new-members/</guid><description>June, 2023
We are delighted to announce the election of our new InnerSource Commons (ISC) Foundation Members: Guilherme Dellagustin, Yuki Hattori, Bill Higgins and Katie Schueths.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Operational Planning Advocating the Strategic Value of an ISPO</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-05-31/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-05-31/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Thomas Forment from Komyu discuss Beyond Operational Planning: Advocating the Strategic Value of an InnerSource Program Office (ISPO)</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2023-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2023-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May, 2023
The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of a new Board of Directors and Officers comprising of Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair), Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (President), Russ Rutledge (Vice President) Tom Sadler (Secretary), Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary), Matt Cobby, Georg Grütter, Yuki Hattori, and Dmitrii Sugrobov.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Conflict</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-05-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-05-23/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Ciara Flanagan from ResetRP discuss how best to deal with conflict when we meet it in relation to InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>Running an OSPO the Open Source / InnerSource way</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-04-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-04-26/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Thomas Steenbergen from EPAM Systems share the story of how he chose to use industry collaboration and InnerSource as the way to address open source challenges.</description></item><item><title>State of InnerSource 2023</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-04-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-04-25/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Clare Dillon from InnerSource Commons share the results from this year&amp;rsquo;s survey in The State of InnerSource 2023.</description></item><item><title>Using Backstage as an InnerSource Portal</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-03-21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-03-21/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear Miguel Capitao from Deutsche Bank discuss how he uses Backstage as an InnerSource portal.</description></item><item><title>Trouver les arguments pour l’InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-03-09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-03-09/</guid><description>Join us for our first french-speaking community call when Gilles Gravier will show us how to present the business case for InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>Implementing InnerSource Metrics</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-03-08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-03-08/</guid><description>Join us on this community call to hear how Luis Cañas-Díaz from Bitergia is Implenting InnerSource Metrics.</description></item><item><title>Spelling InnerSource - a history</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-02-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-02-28/</guid><description>Join us at this community call to hear the history of the InnerSource Spelling from InnerSource Commons founder, Danese Cooper.</description></item><item><title>Building the Case for InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-02-08/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-02-08/</guid><description>In this session, Gilles Gravier from Wipro will explore the value propositions for InnerSource that get buy-in from senior leadership in organizations.</description></item><item><title>Decision Making at Scale for InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-01-18/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-01-18/</guid><description>InnerSource projects are powerful because they scale. They scale in impact and in quality and function.</description></item><item><title>Applying OpenChain and SBOMs for InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-01-10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2023-01-10/</guid><description>In this session we discuss how to apply OpenChain and SBOMs for InnerSource. we will look at applying open source industry best practices and standards.</description></item><item><title>ISC End of Year community call</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-12-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-12-14/</guid><description>For our ISC End of Year community call we will be celebrating our wins and examine our learnings.</description></item><item><title>An ISPO Working Group for the ISC</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-12-06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-12-06/</guid><description>This session will discuss forming an ISC working group to document challenges that we have, and plan that solutions to those challenges are implemented as much as possible in the open.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Summit 2022</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2022/</guid><description>Registrations are Now Open 16th &amp;amp; 17th November 2022 - online Join us at the world&amp;rsquo;s leading gathering of InnerSource practitioners.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Halloween Spook-tacular</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-11-08/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-11-08/</guid><description>This community call will be the second of two Halloween Spook-tacular calls discussing InnerSource Horror Stories!</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Halloween Spook-tacular</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-10-26/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-10-26/</guid><description>This community call will be the first of two Halloween Spook-tacular calls discussing InnerSource Horror Stories!</description></item><item><title>How to Create an InnerSource Culture</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-10-04/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-10-04/</guid><description>This presentation will talk about culture, the importance of building the right foundation and proven tips you can leverage to create for a lasting Innersource culture.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource to Open Source</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-09-21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-09-21/</guid><description>InnerSource to Open Source - taking the next step. This session will share experiences from both Matt Cobby &amp;amp; Mishari Muqbil on taking the path from Inner to Open Source and the benefits of taking that journey.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Gathering</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/gathering-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/gathering-2022/</guid><description>Join us for the first post-COVID in-person gathering of the InnerSource Commons community!</description></item><item><title>Demystifying OSPOs</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-09-05/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-09-05/</guid><description>During this talk, Ana Jimenez Santamaria will share some of the insights from the last OSPO survey from the TODO Group and discuss where and how InnerSource could accelerate open source adoption within an organization&amp;rsquo;s open-source journey.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Catchup</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-08-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-08-16/</guid><description>Join us for a Lean Coffee event designed to facilitate informal learning and sharing of insights, challenges and best practices in a safe environment, which will surface the areas of interest that we will focus on in future events.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Catchup</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-07-13/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-07-13/</guid><description>Join us for a Lean Coffee event designed to facilitate informal learning and sharing of insights, challenges and best practices in a safe environment, which will surface the areas of interest that we will focus on in future events.</description></item><item><title>FINOS InnerSource Panel</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-06-21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-06-21/</guid><description>In place of our usual community call, on June, 21st (5pm BST / 6pm CEST / 9:30 pm IST/ 12am PST) we are partnering with FINOS to bring you a Panel discussion on the topic of InnerSource in Financial Services.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Culture Change</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-06-08/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-06-08/</guid><description>Join us for a fascinating panel discussion on InnerSource Culture Change where Paul Fijnvandraat (Microsoft), Harleen Kaur (Microsoft), Mishari Muqbil (Zymple) and Clare Dillon (InnerSource Commons) will share their experiences on this topic.</description></item><item><title>Incentivizing Culture Change</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-05-24/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-05-24/</guid><description>Join us for a stimulating panel discussion on Incentivizing Culture Change, where Micaela Eller (IBM), Wolfgang Gehring (Mercedes Benz) and Katie Schueths (Indeed) will share their own experiences on this topic.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Services Directory</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/community/services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/community/services/</guid><description>InnerSource サービスディレクトリへようこそ。我々は、3つのカテゴリに収まるインナーソースサービスを提供する企業のリストを収集しています。その範囲はツール、コンサルティングサービス、およびトレーニングサービスにわたります。 サービスリストに追加したい場合は、 info@innersourcecommons.org に電子メールを送信してください。
我々は、このページ上の情報が常に正確かつ有用であることを保証するために最善を尽くします。しかし、以下に記載されているリンクやコンテンツは、InnerSource Commons による推奨や推薦を表すものではなく、リンク先の組織と何らかの関連性を持っていることを意味するものではありません。
会社 サービスの種類 サービスの説明 トレーニングとコンサルティングサービス Bayaveはオープンソース、インナーソース、およびプロダクト戦略に関するトレーニングとコンサルティングサービスを提供しています。詳細は弊社ウェブサイト https://bayave.com/ をご覧いただくか、直接 info@bayave.</description></item><item><title>The Role of Middle Management</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-05-11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-05-11/</guid><description>Join us for a fascinating panel discussion on the role of Middle Management featuring Matt Cobby (Deloitte), Danese Cooper (InnerSource Commons), Jamie Strusz (GitHub), and Jack Yang (Trend Micro).</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2022-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2022-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May, 2022
The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of a new Board of Directors comprising of Danese Cooper (Chairperson), Isabel Drost-Fromm (President), Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (Vice President), Tom Sadler (Secretary), Jacob Green, Georg Grütter, Johannes Tigges, Sebastian Spier, and Klaas-Jan Stol.</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2022-05-new-members/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2022-05-new-members/</guid><description>May, 2022
We are delighted to announce the election of new InnerSource Commons Foundation Members: Matt Cobby, Cristina Coffey, Zack Koppert, Mishari Muqbil and Igor Zubiaurre.</description></item><item><title>Creating Platforms with InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-04-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-04-26/</guid><description>Join us on April 26th when Hong Phuc Dang (FOSSASIA) and Dr Lorraine Morgan (NUIG) will discuss their research at Zalando, Philips Healthcare and PayPal into Creating Platforms with InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>State of InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-04-13/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-04-13/</guid><description>Come along to our next event where Klaas-Jan Stol (University College Cork) and Clare Dillon (InnerSource Commons) will discuss the results of the State of InnerSource 2021 Report.</description></item><item><title>Community Building in the context of InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-03-29/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-03-29/</guid><description>Join us for our next event where Shilla Saebi (Comcast), Georg J.P. Link (Bitergia) and Isabel Drost-Fromm (Europace) will discuss Community Building in the context of InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>Transfer Pricing for InnerSource Projects</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-03-16/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-03-16/</guid><description>Come along to our next Community Call on Transfer Pricing for InnerSource Projects where we will be joined by Gijs Meijer (ING Bank), Wolf Salden (ING Bank) and Jesus Gutierrez (Grupo Santander) where they will discuss the tax implications of transferring IP when conducting InnerSource projects</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Security</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-02-22/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-02-22/</guid><description>Come along to our next Community Call to hear from Vishal Kulshrestha (Verizon), Elspeth Minty (Morgan Stanley) &amp;amp; Conley Rogers (GitLab) discussing the way they have tackled the challenge of developing securely while collaborating across the business.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource ROI &amp; People Strategies</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-02-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-02-02/</guid><description>In this session, we will be joined by Matt Cobby from Deloitte, Daniel Izquierdo from Bitergia and Swapnil Kulkarni from Nuance who will be sharing their experiences of InnerSource ROI &amp;amp; Convincing Leaders</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Programs &amp; People Strategies</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-01-18/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2022-01-18/</guid><description>Join us for our first InnerSource Community Call of 2022 where we will discuss the topic of InnerSource Programs &amp;amp; People Strategies.</description></item><item><title>2021 Year End Call</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-12-14/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-12-14/</guid><description>Join us for our Year End InnerSource Commons Community Call to connect and celebrate a great year past and agree on priorities for 2022.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Outstanding Contributors 2021</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-11-outstanding-contributors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-11-outstanding-contributors/</guid><description>The Internet, November 19th, 2021
2021 has been a significant year for InnerSource Commons. With over 50 active contributors across the 3 working groups, the community has significantly increased its activity and achieved some amazing results.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Summit 2021</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-2021/</guid><description>17th and 18th November 2021, online Get your ticket now! Join us at the world&amp;rsquo;s largest InnerSource Conference!</description></item><item><title>Strategies for Kick-starting InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-10-20/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-10-20/</guid><description>Join us for an InnerSource Commons Community Call where we will discuss Strategies to Kick-start InnerSource in enterprise organizations with Jesús Alonso Gutierrez from Grupo Santander and Shishir Saxena from Fidelity.</description></item><item><title>Clare Dillon Joins InnerSource Commons as First Executive Director</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-10-first-executive-director/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-10-first-executive-director/</guid><description>The Internet, October 19th, 2021
The InnerSource Commons Foundation (ISC), the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost community for InnerSource practitioners, today announced Clare Dillon as Executive Director.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Patterns</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-10-05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-10-05/</guid><description>Join us for an InnerSource Commons Community Call where we will discuss the topic of InnerSource Patterns with Gil Yehuda from US Bank, Fei Wan from Comcast and Sebastian Spier from Meltwater.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons announces first Partners and Supporters helping to scale the efforts in creating and sharing InnerSource knowledge</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-09-sponsors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-09-sponsors/</guid><description>The Internet, September 22, 2021
InnerSource Commons, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest community of InnerSource practitioners, today announced seven new Partners and Supporters at the launch of their new Sponsorship Program.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource in the Enterprise</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-09-21/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-09-21/</guid><description>Join us for an InnerSource Commons Community Call where we will discuss the topic of InnerSource in the Enterprise - Stories from National Australia Bank and Huawei with Matt Cobby and Willem Jiang.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource in Action</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-09-07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-09-07/</guid><description>Join us for an InnerSource Commons Community Call where we will discuss the topic of InnerSource in Action with Georg Grütter from Bosch and Isabel Drost-Fromm from Europace.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource &amp; Discoverability</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-07-06/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-07-06/</guid><description>Join us for an InnerSource Commons Community Call where we will discuss the topic of InnerSource &amp;amp; Discoverability with Michael Graf and Guilherme Delagustin from SAP.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource &amp; DevOps</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-06-01/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-06-01/</guid><description>In this session we will be joined by Fei Wan from Comcast, Steph Egan from BBC and Tom Sadler from BBC who will be sharing their experiences of implementing DevOps with InnerSource.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource in Government</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-05-04/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-05-04/</guid><description>In this session we will be joined by Zack Koppert from GitHub and some of the InnerSource Community, who will be sharing their experiences of how to implement InnerSource in government organizations.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Metrics, Value &amp; ROI Community Call</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-04-06/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/meetup-2021-04-06/</guid><description>In this session we will be joined by Joe Patrao from Bloomberg and Daniel Izquierdo from Bitergia, who will be sharing their experiences of how to measure the success of your InnerSource implementation.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Joins FINOS</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-03-finos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-03-finos/</guid><description>InnerSource Commons to Further Collaboration Within Fintech Organizations We are delighted that to announce that InnerSource Commons is now an associate member of FINOS, the Fintech Open Source Foundation.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons announces the appointment of a new Board of Directors</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-03-new-board/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2021-03-new-board/</guid><description>The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of a new Board of Directors comprising of Danese Cooper (Chairperson), Isabel Drost-Fromm (President), Georg Grutter (Vice President), Cedric Williams (Treasurer), Russell Rutledge (Secretary), Johannes Tigges (Assistant Secretary), Maximilian Capraro, Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar and Jacob Green.</description></item><item><title>APAC Virtual Summit 2020</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-apac-dec-2020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-apac-dec-2020/</guid><description>2nd and 3rd December 2020, online - event site! The 12th InnerSource Commons Summit was our first summit timed for our growing APAC community.</description></item><item><title>Statement of Support of the EC Adoption of InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2020-10-ec-innersource-adoption/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2020-10-ec-innersource-adoption/</guid><description>The InnerSource Commons welcomes the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s new Open Source Software Strategy 2020-2023 highlighting how InnerSource (the creation of working cultures based on open source) is an integral part of a robust open source strategy and ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>North American Fall Virtual Summit 2020</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2020/</guid><description>15th and 16th September 2020, online! The 11th InnerSource Commons Summit stayed online thanks to the success of the ISC Online Spring Summit 2020.</description></item><item><title>Spring Summit 2020</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2020/</guid><description>14th to 15th April 2020, online The 10th InnerSource Commons Summit took place in your living room!</description></item><item><title>Incorporation of InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2020-02-incorporation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/announcements/2020-02-incorporation/</guid><description>Press Release: Incorporation of InnerSource Commons Foundation The InnerSource Commons Foundation (ISC) was incorporated on February 19th, 2020 and is taking steps to become a 501(c)(3) public charity.</description></item><item><title>Fall Summit 2019</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2019/</guid><description>MossLabs.io, St. Francis Neighborhood Center, Maryland Institute College of Art, &amp;amp; The Johns Hopkins University proudly welcome the InnerSource Commons community to Baltimore.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Day @ OSCON 2019</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/oscon-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/oscon-2019/</guid><description>InnerSource day at OSCON is a gathering of industry practitioners discussing real-world implementations of this community-inspired, transformational open source approach to software development within the enterprise.</description></item><item><title>Spring Summit 2019</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2019/</guid><description>9th to 11th April 2019 in Galway, Ireland Follow us on Twitter and Facebook and share your experience of the Summit.</description></item><item><title>Fall Summit 2018</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2018/</guid><description>October 3-5, 2018 in Islandia, New York, USA Event That&amp;rsquo;s an official wrap on the InnerSource Commons Fall Summit!</description></item><item><title>Spring Summit 2018</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2018/</guid><description>May 16-18 Wed-Fri near Stuttgart, Germany Pictures and Videos The ISC.S6 is a wrap! Thanks to all attendees for making this summit such an engaging and interesting one!</description></item><item><title>Fall Summit 2017</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2017/</guid><description>September 27-29 Wed-Fri in Chicago (Naperville, IL), USA Fifty nine people representing twenty two companies and institutions were present for the InnerSource Commons Fall Summit 2017 in Naperville, IL, USA.</description></item><item><title>Spring Summit 2017</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2017/</guid><description>April 18-20 in Geneva, Switzerland Join us for the next InnerSource Commons Summit in Geneva, Switzerland.</description></item><item><title>Fall Summit 2016</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-fall-2016/</guid><description>September 28-30 in Boston, USA Join us for the next InnerSource Commons Summit in Boston, USA.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource @ OSCON US 2016</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/oscon-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/oscon-2016/</guid><description>May 16-19 in Austin, Texas There are several opportunities to learn more about InnerSource at OSCON US this year.</description></item><item><title>Spring Summit 2016</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-spring-2016/</guid><description>April 21-22 2016 in London, England Companies today already understand that Open Source is necessary.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-summit-2025-di/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/isc-summit-2025-di/</guid><description>Summit Inclusion &amp;amp; Accessibility All attendees, speakers, sponsors, and volunteers at InnerSource Summit are required to agree with the [InnerSource Commons Code of Conduct](https://innersourcecommons.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/scaling/markmap-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/learn/scaling/markmap-content/</guid><description>Scaling InnerSource InnerSource Program Office Executive Sponsorship Pattern: Review Committee Pattern: Start as an Experiment Dedicated Staffing Pattern: Dedicated Community Leader InnerSource Program as an InnerSource Project (lead by example) Governance of InnerSource Programs Company leadership support Unblock policy constraints Pattern: Contracted Contributor Pattern: InnerSource License SBOMs for InnerSource projects Applying OpenChain and SBOMs for InerSource Accelerated contributions Systems Book: Managing InnerSource Projects, chapters Infrastructure and Tooling Pattern: Service vs.</description></item><item><title>2020-05-13</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-05-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-05-13/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2020-05-13, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CEST / 11 a.m. - noon CDT</description></item><item><title>2020-06-10</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-06-10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-06-10/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2020-06-10, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CEST / 11 a.m. - noon CDT</description></item><item><title>2020-11-18</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-11-18/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-11-18/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2020-11-18, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CET / 9 a.m. - 10 a.</description></item><item><title>2020-12-16</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-12-16/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2020-12-16/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2020-12-16, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CET / 9 a.m. - 10 a.</description></item><item><title>2021-01-20</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-01-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-01-20/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-01-20, 7 p.m - 8 p.m. CET / 10 a.m. - 11 a.</description></item><item><title>2021-03-18</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-03-18/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-03-18/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-03-18, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CEST / 11 a.m. - noon CDT</description></item><item><title>2021-04-21</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-04-21/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-04-21/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-04-21, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CEST / 11 a.m. - noon CDT</description></item><item><title>2021-05-26</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-05-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-05-26/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-05-26, 6 p.m - 7 p.m. CEST / 11 a.m. - noon CDT Call to order 18:07 CEST Adjourned 19:00 CEST Role Call Directors Present Jacob Green Danese Cooper (Chair) Isabel Drost-Fromm (President) Georg Grütter (Vice President) Daniel Izquierdo Russell Rutledge (Secretary) Johannes Tigges (Assistant Secretary) Maximilian Capraro Cedric Williams (Treasurer) Directors Absent None Members Present Sebastian Spier Clare Dillon Votes Taken Danese (Cedric seconds) moves to find and promote a VP of FINOS interaction on a trial period of 6 months pending review of the results.</description></item><item><title>2021-06-23</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-06-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-06-23/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-06-23, 7 p.m - 8 p.m. CET / 10 a.m. - 11 a.</description></item><item><title>2021-07-21</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-07-21/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-07-21/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-07-21, 7 p.m - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 a.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2021-09-22</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-09-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-09-22/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-09-22, 7 p.m - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 a.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2021-10-21</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-10-21/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-10-21/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-10-21, 7 p.m - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2021-12-02</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-12-02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2021-12-02/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2021-12-02, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CET / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-01-13</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-01-13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-01-13/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-01-13, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CET / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-02-10</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-02-10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-02-10/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-02-10, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CET / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-03-07</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-03-07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-03-07/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-03-07, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CET / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-04-04</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-04-04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-04-04/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-04-04, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CET / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-04-19</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-04-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-04-19/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-04-19, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-05-24</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-05-24/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-05-24/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-05-24, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-06-20</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-06-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-06-20/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-06-20, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-08-19</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-08-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-08-19/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-08-19, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-09-22</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-09-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-09-22/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-09-22, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-10-24</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-10-24/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-10-24/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-10-24, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-11-28</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-11-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-11-28/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-11-28, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2022-12-22</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-12-22/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2022-12-22/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2022-12-22, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2023-01-26</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-01-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-01-26/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-01-26, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2023-02-23</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-02-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-02-23/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-02-23, 7 p.m. - 8 p.m. CET / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2023-03-23</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-03-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-03-23/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-03-23, 9 a.m. - 10 a.m. CET / 2 a.m. - 3 a.</description></item><item><title>2023-04-27</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-04-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-04-27/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-04-27, 7 p.m - 8 p.m. CEST / 12 p.m. - 1 p.</description></item><item><title>2023-05-25</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-05-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-05-25/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-05-25, 2 p.m. - 3 p.m. CEST
Call to order 14:02 CEST Adjourned 14:41 CEST Next meeting 2023-06-29: 7 PM CEST Roll call Directors and Officers Present Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair) Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (President) Russ Rutledge (Vice President) Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary) Matt Cobby Georg Gruetter Yuki Hattori Dmitrii Sugrobov Directors and Officers Absent Tom Sadler (Secretary) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Members Present Clare Dillon (Executive Director) Votes Taken No proposals were voted on.</description></item><item><title>2023-06-29</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-06-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-06-29/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-06-29, 9am - 10am CEST
Call to order 9:03 CEST Adjourned 10:00 CEST Next meeting 2023-07-27: 2pm CEST Roll call Directors and Officers Present Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair) Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (President) Tom Sadler (Secretary) Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary) Matt Cobby Yuki Hattori Georg Grütter (by proxy of Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar) Directors and Officers Absent Russ Rutledge (Vice President) Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Dmitrii Sugrobov Members Present Clare Dillon (Executive Director) Votes Taken Vote on having Russell Rutledge as new Executive Director of the InnerSource Commons Foundation starting on the 1st of July 2023.</description></item><item><title>2023-07-27</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-07-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-07-27/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-07-27, 2pm - 3pm CEST
Call to order: 14:06 CEST Adjourned: 15:01 CEST Next Meeting: 2023-08-31, 9am CEST Roll call Directors and Officers Present Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Matt Cobby Yuki Hattori Dmitrii Sugrobov Georg Grütter Directors and Officers Absent Tom Sadler (Secretary) Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary) Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chairperson) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Votes Taken none</description></item><item><title>2023-08-31</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-08-31/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-08-31/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-08-31, 9am CEST
Call to order: 9:05 CEST Adjourned: 9:42 CEST Next Meeting: 2023-09-28, 2pm CEST Roll call Directors and Officers Present Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chairperson) Matt Cobby Yuki Hattori Dmitrii Sugrobov Georg Grütter Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary) Tom Sadler (Secretary) (by proxy of Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar) Directors and Officers Absent Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Votes Taken Vote on adding Katie Schueths as new Board Member.</description></item><item><title>2023-09-28</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-09-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-09-28/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-09-28, 2pm CEST
Call to order: 2:07pm CEST Adjourned: 2:58pm CEST Next Meeting: 2023-10-26, 9am CEST Roll call Directors and Officers Present Matt Cobby Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair) (by Proxy of Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar) Georg Grütter Yuki Hattori Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Tom Sadler (Secretary) Katie Scheuths Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary) Dmitrii Sugrobov Directors and Officers Absent Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Votes Taken Vote to elect Vice President:</description></item><item><title>2023-10-26</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-10-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-10-26/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2023-10-26, 9am CEST
Call to order: 9:06am CEST Adjourned: 9:45am CEST Next Meeting: 2023-11-30, 2pm CET Roll call Directors and Officers Present Matt Cobby (from 9:11) Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair) Georg Grütter (by Proxy of Tom Sadler until 9:34) Yuki Hattori Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) (by Proxy of Isabel Drost-Fromm until 9:12) Tom Sadler (Secretary) Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary, Vice President) Dmitrii Sugrobov Directors and Officers Absent Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Katie Schueths Votes Taken Vote on proposed change to bylaws regarding Directors&amp;rsquo; compensation:</description></item><item><title>2023-11-30</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-11-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2023-11-30/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2023-11-30, 2:07pm CET Adjourned: 3:01pm CET Next Meeting: 2023-12-21, 9am CET Roll call Directors and Officers Present Matt Cobby Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair) Georg Grütter Yuki Hattori Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Tom Sadler (Secretary) Katie Schueths Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary, Vice President) Directors and Officers Absent Silona Bonewald (Treasurer) Maximilian Capraro (Assistant Treasurer) Dmitrii Sugrobov Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2024-01-25</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-01-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-01-25/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-01-25, 2:07pm CET Adjourned: 2:53pm CET Next Meeting: 2024-02-29, 9am CET Roll call Directors and Officers Present Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Yuki Hattori Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Tom Sadler (Treasurer) Katie Schueths Directors and Officers Absent Matt Cobby (Secretary) Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair) Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary, Vice President) Dmitrii Sugrobov Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2024-03-28</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-03-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-03-28/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-03-28, 14:09 CET Adjourned: 14:52 CET Next Meeting: 2024-05-02, 07:00 CET Roll call Directors and Officers Present Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary, Vice President) Yuki Hattori Georg Gruetter (Assistant Treasurer) Katie Schueths Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Directors and Officers Absent Matt Cobby Tom Sadler (Assistant Secrtary) Danese Cooper Clare Dillon Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2024-04-25</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-04-25/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-04-25/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-04-25, 5:07pm AEST Adjourned: 6pm AEST Next Meeting: Thursday, 30 May 2024 at 12:00:00 UTC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Clare Dillon Katie Schueths Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Matt Cobby (Secretary) Sebastian Spier Tom Sadler (Treasurer) Yuki Hattori (Vice President) Directors and Officers Absent Danese Cooper Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) - Proxied by Clare Dillon Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Votes Taken Motion to nominate Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar as President.</description></item><item><title>2024-05-30</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-05-30/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-05-30/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-05-30, 12:15 GMT Adjourned: 13:12 GMT Next Meeting: 2024-06-27, 7:00 GMT Roll call Directors and Officers Present Danese Cooper Clare Dillon Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Yuki Hattori (Vice President) Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Katie Schueths (Assistant Secretary) Directors and Officers Absent Matt Cobby (Secretary) Tom Sadler (Treasurer) (Proxied by Clare Dillon) Sebastian Spier Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2024-06-27</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-06-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-06-27/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Called to order: 2024-06-27, 9:05 AM CEST Adjourned: 2024-06-27, 9:41 AM CEST Next Meeting: 2024-07-25, 12:00 UTC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Yuki Hattori (Vice President) Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Katie Schueths (Assistant Secretary) Matt Cobby (Secretary) Directors and Officers Absent Clare Dillon Tom Sadler (Treasurer) Danese Cooper Sebastian Spier Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2024-07-27</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-07-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-07-27/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2024-07-27, 4 p.m. - 5 p.m. CEST / XX p.m. - XX p.</description></item><item><title>2024-08-29</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-08-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-08-29/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting 2024-08-29, 11 a.m. - 12 p.m. CEST
Call to order 11:07 CEST Adjourned 11:59 CEST Next meeting 2024-09-26, 4 p.</description></item><item><title>2024-09-26</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-09-26/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-09-26/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-09-26, 14:08 UTC Adjourned: 14:54 UTC Next Meeting: TBC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Clare Dillon Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Yuki Hattori (Vice-President) Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Katie Schueths (Assistant Secretary) Directors and Officers Absent Matt Cobby (Secretary) (Proxied by Katie Schueths) Tom Sadler (Treasurer) Sebastian Spier Danese Cooper Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2024-11-26</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-11-28/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-11-28/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-11-26, 14:08 UTC Adjourned: 14:41 UTC Next Meeting: 2024-12-19, 9:00 AM UTC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Yuki Hattori (Vice-President) Tom Sadler (Treasurer) (proxy for Georg Grütter) Clare Dillon (proxy for Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar) Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) (joined at 14:22 UTC) Directors and Officers Absent Matt Cobby (Secretary) Sebastian Spier Katie Schueths Danese Cooper Guests Present Lori Landesman Votes Taken Motion: The board would formally like to offer everyone involved in organizing and running the InnerSource summit our thank and congratulations on another fantastic event!</description></item><item><title>2024-12-19</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-12-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2024-12-19/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2024-12-19, 9:05 UTC Adjourned: 9:59 UTC Next Meeting: TBC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Matt Cobby (Secretary) Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Yuki Hattori (Vice-President) Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Tom Sadler (Treasurer) Directors and Officers Absent Katie Schueths (Assistant Secretary) Clare Dillon Sebastian Spier Danese Cooper Russel Rutledge (Executive Director) Votes Taken None</description></item><item><title>2025-02-27</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2025-02-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2025-02-27/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 2025-02-27, 09:05 UTC Adjourned: 10:02 UTC Next Meeting: 2025-03-27, 14:00 UTC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Daniel Izquierdo-Cortazar (President) Matt Cobby (Secretary) / proxy for Georg Grütter Katie Schueths Clare Dillon Sebastian Spier Yuki Hattori (Vice-President) Directors and Officers Absent Georg Grütter (Assistant Treasurer) Tom Sadler (Treasurer) Danese Cooper Guests Present Cristina Coffey Votes Taken none</description></item><item><title>2025-05-29</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2025-05-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2025-05-29/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 14:00 UTC Adjourned: 15:00 UTC Next meeting: 2025-06-26, 09:00 UTC Roll call Directors and Officers Present</description></item><item><title>2025-07-31</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2025-07-31/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/board/2025-07-31/</guid><description>Date and Time of Meeting Call to order: 14:03 UTC Adjourned: 15:00 UTC Next meeting: 2025-08-28, 08:58 UTC Roll call Directors and Officers Present Yuki Hattori (President) Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (Chair) Jeff Bailey (Assistant Secretary) Georg Grutter (Treasurer) Clare Dillon (Vice-President) Russ Rutledge (Executive Director) Directors and Officers Absent Matt Cobby (Secretary) (proxied by Yuki Hattori) Members Present Cristina Coffey Votes Taken No proposals were voted on.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons 行動規範</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/codeofconduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/codeofconduct/</guid><description>宣言 私たちは、メンバー、貢献者、リーダーとして、年齢、体格、目に見える・見えない障がい、民族性、性特性、性自認・表現、経験レベル、教育、社会経済状況、国籍、容姿、人種、宗教、性自認・志向にかかわらず、誰にとってもハラスメントのないコミュニティへの参加を実現することを誓約します。
私たちは、オープンで歓迎に満ちた、多様で包括的かつ健全なコミュニティに貢献する方法で行動し、交流することを誓います。
基準 例えば、私たちのコミュニティに貢献する行動としては、次のようなことがあります。
他の人々に対する共感と優しさを示す 異なる意見、見解、および経験を尊重する 建設的なフィードバックを与え、優雅に受け入れる 私たちの過ちによって影響を受けた人々に対して責任を取り、その経験から学ぶ 私たち個人だけでなく、全体のコミュニティにとって最善であることに焦点を当てる 不適切な行動の例としては、次のようなことがあります。
性的な言葉やイメージの使用、およびあらゆる種類の性的な注目やアプローチ トロール、侮辱的なコメント、および個人的または政治的な攻撃 公共またはプライベートなハラスメント 他人の私人情報（物理的なアドレスや電子メールアドレスなど）を明示的な許可なく公開する 専門的な環境で不適切とされるほどの行為 執行責任 コミュニティ・リーダーは、私たちが許容する行動基準を明確にし、それを実施する責任があります。また、不適切、脅迫的、攻撃的、または有害と判断される行動に対しては、適切かつ公正な是正措置を取ります。</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Patterns</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/patterns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/patterns/</guid><description/></item><item><title>InnerSourcerers Map</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/map/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/map/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ISC 101</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/isc-101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/isc-101/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Local Gatherings</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/local-gatherings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/local-gatherings/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Members</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/members/</guid><description>The InnerSource Commons (ISC) community is open to all. Some community participants go above and beyond, and may be invited to become an ISC Member.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft DevOps Dojo InnerSource Case Study</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/stories/microsoft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/stories/microsoft/</guid><description>Summary When done right, InnerSource is one of the most effective ways to release trapped value in the enterprise.</description></item><item><title>Our Sponsors</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/sponsors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/sponsors/</guid><description>Our Partners Analog Devices “At Analog Devices, we believe strongly in the power of InnerSource to accelerate innovation and improve developer experience.</description></item><item><title>Page Not Found</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/404.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/404.html</guid><description/></item><item><title>Past Summits</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/past-summits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/events/past-summits/</guid><description>InnerSource Summit 2024 Registrations are Now Open 20th &amp; 21st November 2024 - online. Join us at the world’s leading gathering of InnerSource practitioners.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/privacy/</guid><description>InnerSource Commons is an independent non-for-profit organisation that creates and shares knowledge about InnerSource for its members.</description></item><item><title>slack</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/slack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/slack/</guid><description/></item><item><title>お問い合わせ</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/ja/about/contact/</guid><description> 問い合わせの最速かつ最良の方法は、Slackに参加し、#general チャンネルで質問をすることです。 Slackに参加する また、 info@innersourcecommons.org 宛てにメールでお問い合わせください。 つながる
コミュニティでのアクションの大部分は、Slack Channelで行われます。また、InnerSource Commonsのニュース、イベント、活動については、以下のニュースレターにサインアップし、TwitterとLinkedInでフォローし、YouTubeチャンネルを購読することで、最新の情報を入手することができます。
ニュースレターにサインアップする
Read previous newsletters here</description></item></channel></rss>