<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on InnerSource Commons</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on InnerSource Commons</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/01/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>This Learning Path gives an introduction to InnerSource.
InnerSource is the application of open source practices and principles to software development within the enterprise.
InnerSource software remains proprietary to the company, but within it is open for anyone to use it and contribute to it.
This strategy enables wide and effective collaboration, producing software that is responsive and nimble to the changing needs of its many internal stakeholders.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Problems Does InnerSource Solve?</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/02/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>InnerSource encourages and rewards collaboration and code reuse with anyone, regardless of their position in a company&amp;#8217;s organizational structure.
This approach differs from what is seen in traditional organizations where ideas and work product tend to stay trapped within the boundaries of the internal corporate hierarchy and its silos.
Let&amp;#8217;s explore one situation that gives an example of this idea.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Does InnerSource Work?</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/03/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>Let&amp;#8217;s say that team A uses software produced by team B.
Team A submits a feature request to team B, but team B isn&amp;#8217;t able to implement that feature in time for team A.
In an InnerSource setting, if team A can&amp;#8217;t get this feature request then it submits a pull request instead.
That is to say team A implements the feature directly in team B&amp;#8217;s software and submits a pull request with the code changes.
Team B partners to review and accept the submitted code.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What Are The Benefits of InnerSource?</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/04/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>There are many benefits to collaborating via InnerSource.
InnerSource gives a company a scalable strategy for &lt;strong>guest teams to get feature requests when they need them&lt;/strong> without the long-term burden of maintenance.
The company as a whole wins as the time of guest teams is put into code that others can use.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>InnerSource Principles</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/05/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>Every company, team, project, and individual is different.
Because of that fact, the exact way that the concept of InnerSource works will vary from one situation to another.
At its core, however, are four principles that form the bedrock of any successful instance of InnerSource.
These principles have inspiration in successful open source projects and are required in order for InnerSource to achieve the benefits described earlier.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Conclusion</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/06/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>In this learning path, we&amp;#8217;ve given an introduction to InnerSource.
InnerSource applies open source best practices and principles to internal software development.
It gives an additional option to consumers when producing teams are not able to deliver a needed feature request.
Successful InnerSource involves a &lt;a href="https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/product-owner">&lt;em>product owner&lt;/em>&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/trusted-committer">&lt;em>trusted committer&lt;/em>&lt;/a> from the &lt;strong>host team&lt;/strong> as well as a &lt;a href="https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/contributor">&lt;em>contributor&lt;/em>&lt;/a> from the &lt;strong>guest team&lt;/strong>.
Done effectively, InnerSource brings many benefits to both participating teams.
They key principles upon-which effective InnerSource works are &lt;strong>voluntary code contribution&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>prioritized mentorship&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/07/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>To conclude the Introduction segment of the Learning Path, here are some Frequently Asked Questions people have when embarking on their InnerSource journey.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Is InnerSource Right for My Project?</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/08/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/08/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>InnerSource is the application of open source principles to company-internal software development. Done right, it unblocks progress and eases adoption of shared services and modules.
This article contains guidance and questions to ask yourself when considering adoption of an InnerSource approach to running your project.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The InnerSource Mentality</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/09/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/09/</guid><description>&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>InnerSource helps when there are multiple teams at our company that have a shared need - business or technical.
We want one shared project that all can leverage.
This sharing allows each team to spend as much time as possible in their unique business area instead of reinventing what someone has done before.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Workbook</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/workbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/learn/learning-path/introduction/workbook/</guid><description>&lt;div class="sect2">
&lt;h3 id="_video_introduction_to_innersource">Video: Introduction to InnerSource&lt;/h3>
&lt;div class="sect3">
&lt;h4 id="_segment_what_problems_does_innersource_solve">SEGMENT: What Problems Does InnerSource Solve?&lt;/h4>
&lt;div class="paragraph">
&lt;p>TIP:
More than one answer may be correct in some questions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>