<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Announcements on InnerSource Commons</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/</link><description>Recent content in Announcements on InnerSource Commons</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>InnerSource Commons welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2025-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2025-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May 22, 2025
InnerSource Commons Foundation Announces New Board of Directors The InnerSource Commons Foundation is pleased to announce the appointment of its Board of Directors for the upcoming term.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2024-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2024-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May 15, 2024
The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of the Board for the coming year.</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2024-04-new-members/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2024-04-new-members/</guid><description>April 26 2024
We are delighted to announce our new InnerSource Commons (ISC) Foundation Members: Addie Girouard, Brittany Istenes, Chan Voong, Jeff Bailey, Justin Gosses, Thomas Froment and Willem Jiang.</description></item><item><title>Russell Rutledge appointed as new Executive Director of InnerSource Commons</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2023-08-new-executive-director/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2023-08-new-executive-director/</guid><description>August 2023
The InnerSource Commons Foundation (ISC), the world’s foremost community for InnerSource practitioners, today announced Russell Rutledge as its Executive Director.</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2023-06-new-members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2023-06-new-members/</guid><description>June, 2023
We are delighted to announce the election of our new InnerSource Commons (ISC) Foundation Members: Guilherme Dellagustin, Yuki Hattori, Bill Higgins and Katie Schueths.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2023-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2023-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May, 2023
The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of a new Board of Directors and Officers comprising of Isabel Drost-Fromm (Chair), Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (President), Russ Rutledge (Vice President) Tom Sadler (Secretary), Sebastian Spier (Assistant Secretary), Matt Cobby, Georg Grütter, Yuki Hattori, and Dmitrii Sugrobov.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Welcomes our new Board and Officers</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2022-05-new-board-and-officers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2022-05-new-board-and-officers/</guid><description>May, 2022
The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of a new Board of Directors comprising of Danese Cooper (Chairperson), Isabel Drost-Fromm (President), Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar (Vice President), Tom Sadler (Secretary), Jacob Green, Georg Grütter, Johannes Tigges, Sebastian Spier, and Klaas-Jan Stol.</description></item><item><title>New Members Appointed to the InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2022-05-new-members/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2022-05-new-members/</guid><description>May, 2022
We are delighted to announce the election of new InnerSource Commons Foundation Members: Matt Cobby, Cristina Coffey, Zack Koppert, Mishari Muqbil and Igor Zubiaurre.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Outstanding Contributors 2021</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-11-outstanding-contributors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-11-outstanding-contributors/</guid><description>The Internet, November 19th, 2021
2021 has been a significant year for InnerSource Commons. With over 50 active contributors across the 3 working groups, the community has significantly increased its activity and achieved some amazing results.</description></item><item><title>Clare Dillon Joins InnerSource Commons as First Executive Director</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-10-first-executive-director/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-10-first-executive-director/</guid><description>The Internet, October 19th, 2021
The InnerSource Commons Foundation (ISC), the world&amp;rsquo;s foremost community for InnerSource practitioners, today announced Clare Dillon as Executive Director.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons announces first Partners and Supporters helping to scale the efforts in creating and sharing InnerSource knowledge</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-09-sponsors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-09-sponsors/</guid><description>The Internet, September 22, 2021
InnerSource Commons, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest community of InnerSource practitioners, today announced seven new Partners and Supporters at the launch of their new Sponsorship Program.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons Joins FINOS</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-03-finos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-03-finos/</guid><description>InnerSource Commons to Further Collaboration Within Fintech Organizations We are delighted that to announce that InnerSource Commons is now an associate member of FINOS, the Fintech Open Source Foundation.</description></item><item><title>InnerSource Commons announces the appointment of a new Board of Directors</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-03-new-board/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2021-03-new-board/</guid><description>The InnerSource Commons Foundation is delighted to announce the election of a new Board of Directors comprising of Danese Cooper (Chairperson), Isabel Drost-Fromm (President), Georg Grutter (Vice President), Cedric Williams (Treasurer), Russell Rutledge (Secretary), Johannes Tigges (Assistant Secretary), Maximilian Capraro, Daniel Izquierdo Cortazar and Jacob Green.</description></item><item><title>Statement of Support of the EC Adoption of InnerSource</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2020-10-ec-innersource-adoption/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2020-10-ec-innersource-adoption/</guid><description>The InnerSource Commons welcomes the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s new Open Source Software Strategy 2020-2023 highlighting how InnerSource (the creation of working cultures based on open source) is an integral part of a robust open source strategy and ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Incorporation of InnerSource Commons Foundation</title><link>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2020-02-incorporation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://innersourcecommons.org/about/announcements/2020-02-incorporation/</guid><description>Press Release: Incorporation of InnerSource Commons Foundation The InnerSource Commons Foundation (ISC) was incorporated on February 19th, 2020 and is taking steps to become a 501(c)(3) public charity.</description></item></channel></rss>